🎵 Music
🎵 Hello guys and
welcome back to my channel.
I am in Istanbul with my friend Mahdea, and I am so, so excited to be here.
It's my very first time in Turkey.
I've already gotten a little peek into the city because yesterday I was here by myself because Mattea's flight got cancelled last
minute.
She was at the airport, and we were supposed to meet here on Friday.
Today it's Sunday, so we only have two days to explore this huge city.
But guys, yesterday I went to a breakfast spot, and I just ordered some food when all of a sudden a girl in like a friend group came
up to me, and she recognized me from YouTube and Instagram.
She was so, so lovely, and she introduced me to her husband and to her friend, and we sat outside the cafe, and we
chatted, and we got to know each other.
They're all from Turkey and living in Istanbul, so I of course got a lot of local tips, which was amazing.
And later, Ashan and her husband Ali took me on a tour around the neighborhood, which was so sweet, and I'm honestly just so grateful to have met
them.
We also just got along so well because she is also a content creator, and her husband is a videographer, and we were shooting some content
together, and it was so, so much fun.
So yeah, that was a little story from yesterday.
And then Mahda finally arrived yesterday's evening, and we went to have some kebab.
We actually didn't go to sleep until like three in the morning because we were just chatting for hours, but we can't wait to explore
this incredible city.
We already have planned out the day a bit, but we're also just gonna go with the flow and see how the day goes.
Okay guys, your favorite girl is here!
We're back!
We're reunited!
In Istanbul!
It's been a while since we've been together.
Yeah.
So we are really, really excited.
For today, we have a tight schedule.
Yeah, we have to see so many things.
Yeah, so we need to get going.
But I wanted to show you guys a little tour of the apartment.
Yeah, it's very nice.
It's really nice, and we have a big balcony with lots of sunlight.
So yeah, I'm gonna show you guys.
This is the living area or living room, and it leads to a beautiful big terrace or a
balcony.
Oh, very nice to have some sunlight in the morning.
Then we go into...
It's like we're showing our luxury villa or something.
Bathroom.
And our beds.
We would have preferred like a big bed for us together, but this was okay.
We are out and about, and we are gonna have some Turkish breakfast, really excited to try some authentic Turkish
food.
Turkish coffee.
Yes, and Turkish tea as well.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I thought I should show you guys what we are wearing today.
They
just handed us this Turkish tea, and we didn't even order it, so we're very excited to try.
The Turkish breakfast did not disappoint.
No, it was super good.
Oh my god, and the waiter was so, so sweet, and he brought so much food.
I was like, when is this gonna stop?
Oh my goodness.
We sat for like an hour just eating and like so many different dishes, like olives, something sweet, also a lot of things that we were
like, ah, this tastes like feta, but it's a bit different, or this is like this.
And the Turkish coffee was also very good.
It was like a strong americano.
We are like stuffed right now.
We have been eating so much good food, and now we are just gonna walk around in the neighborhood that we are staying in.
We're gonna check out the Galata Tower.
Yeah.
I also spotted a really cool like vintage store yesterday with lots and lots of sunglasses, and we are both wanting a new pair of
sunglasses, and I really think we are gonna find a cool pair of vintage like sunny is there.
So that's like our plan for now.
Yeah.
This is literally sunglass heaven.
I'm not even kidding, guys.
He has so many cool frames here.
We bought sunglasses.
They look so good on Mattea.
I have so few sunglasses.
I never wear them.
These look so good.
I love these.
Mine are a bit funky, a little bit different.
I really like them.
Super cool.
I actually spotted them yesterday, and I was like, I need to come here tomorrow and.
Vlog because I wanted to show you guys.
We just walked over the Galata Bridge, and the views were immaculate.
So beautiful.
Yeah.
We are now in the Sultanahmet.
Was it called Sultanahmet?
We're trying to learn a bit of Turkish.
Here, supposedly, are a lot of historical marks, a lot of mosques, and we're just gonna explore this area.
A lot of history is here, so...
And a lot of people.
Lots and lots of people.
Oh my god, and it's so warm outside.
We are going to visit the
Hagia Sophia Grand Mosque, and this is my first time going to a mosque.
I think mine also, actually.
So we are quite interested to see how it's inside and just learn about, you know, everything around the history, the architecture.
So let's go inside.
So
we
just sat down to have some afternoon snack.
We bought lemonade and a simit.
It's a bread that is in this circle, and it has a lot of sesame seeds.
We're gonna try them out.
Sesame seed bread.
Yeah, it tastes a lot like sesame seeds.
I like bread.
Yeah, it's good.
The lemonade is very good.
Yeah, it's very fresh because it's super warm now.
Yeah, so that was very needed.
Okay, so next destination is Egyptian Bazaar, where they sell like spices, sweets.
Huge.
Yeah, we're really excited to go there and explore because we've heard really great things about this market.
Yeah.
So let's see what we'll find.
We got some hot tea.
I have a pineapple.
And I have pomegranate.
It's very good.
Cheers.
It's really good.
Okay, we need to switch.
Both are so good!
So fresh!
Yeah.
And there's no sugar in them.
No, they use stevia.
Oh, nice!
Super nice.
And then we also got...
Baklava!
Eee!
Pistachio.
Oh, my favorite.
But I haven't tried this one before, but I love pistachios, so...
Okay.
Try.
I like that it's not too sweet.
And it has lots of pistachio flavor.
It
was so much fun to explore the
bazaar, the market, and there were so many different stores selling all types of things.
We bought some Turkish delights.
I've never tried them.
Me neither.
Have you guys seen like Narnia, the movie?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's just like...
Yeah, the ice lady, like the ice queen or something, she has it in the bucket.
I don't know if that's like Turkish delight, but it's like...
I always wanted to try it.
When I was a kid, I was like, I know, it's not so good!
So I've been wanting to try it, and so we bought a bit of that, and then we tried the baklava, like you guys saw.
But the guys at the store were like really, really cute.
So sweet, yeah.
Really sweet.
And they gave us a lucky charm, or like this evil eye.
Yeah, it's gonna protect us from any like evil energy, I guess.
Yeah, they were so sweet.
Really, really sweet.
We just saw the most insane sunset, and I don't know, in Denmark we don't get this beautiful sunsets.
I don't know, it's so strange.
We're sharing the same sun, and we like experiencing it all differently, but here it was incredible.
Yeah, very beautiful.
And I think tomorrow we are maybe gonna try and order like river cruise or something like we did in Budapest, because the views here
are, yeah, stunning, and it was so nice in Budapest to see it from the seaside, you know, like point of view.
It gives you also like a different perspective of the city, and when we don't have a lot of time, it's like nice to see how big the
city is and see the different parts and everything.
Yeah, definitely.
So tomorrow we might do that, but now we are gonna have some dinner.
We are probably gonna have some Turkish food.
We are just trying to figure out where to go, so we're just walking in the Karaköy neighborhood, I think it's called.
We walked over the Galata Bridge, so now we are just trying to figure out where to eat.
We are back home after our lovely dinner.
It was so nice.
We were actually very surprised.
We weren't expecting this type of view over the city.
It was incredible.
We should have arrived a bit earlier, though.
Yeah, for the sunset.
Because for the sunset, it was getting a bit too dark, but still we enjoyed it so.
Much.
And now we wanted to do a little taste test because I just realized we didn't try them before, so we're gonna dig in.
Yeah.
Gooey, gooey, okay.
It's actually quite good.
I like the consistency.
I was kind of like, "Oh my god, I'm choking on it."
But it is kind of like Narnia, actually.
How also you like the bite.
Honestly, I think they used that.
Yeah.
I would guess so.
We need to Google it.
We're going to be so happy that we've tried the Narnia candy.
I'm like impressed.
I like the consistency.
It's quite fun.
I was expecting because how it looks, I was like, "I don't think I'm going to like it."
Yeah.
But then actually it's nice.
It's okay.
Thank you for tuning in.
We're going to go to sleep for the taste test.
And we'll see you guys tomorrow.
Another day!
We're very excited.
We're gonna explore the Asian side.
Yeah.
We heard some, you know, fun things about that part of the city.
It's definitely...
Different.
Yeah.
Because we could definitely feel the difference between the area that we're staying in now.
And after we got to, like, the other side of the city.
Like, over the Galata Bridge.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know.
Like, the atmosphere was totally different.
Like, a lot more tourism.
Yeah.
And, yeah, it was just kind of...
Yeah, it was different.
Yeah, different vibe.
Good night guys, and we'll see you tomorrow!
We made it out of the house.
We are on our way to have breakfast at a cafe called Cafe 6.
The weather is really nice.
We woke up a bit earlier than yesterday because we wanted to explore the whole day.
So let's go and have some coffee and breakfast!
I ordered childir.
It's poached eggs and pita bread and some sauteed spinach and I think garlic yogurt or
something.
And it looks really, really nice.
I ordered the granola with pear compote and banana on top.
Looks really nice.
Very nice.
Cute.
And espresso macchiato.
I was craving coffee, but I just didn't feel like it would fit with like this savory dish, so instead I ordered a lemonade.
It's really good, and it matches my dress.
Yeah.
Matches my hair.
So
we
just took some pictures in the photo booth.
It's kind of funny, and we weren't like prepared at all for the first one.
We were like, "Here's three, two, one."
I think, you know, it's just a memory, and it's fun too.
Got two.
We got two, which was really nice.
We are just walking around here in this neighborhood.
We are gonna check out a store like an antique store that we saved on the map, and I think we're just gonna walk
around a bit, and then in a few hours or like I don't know when, we are gonna take the ferry over to the Asian side.
We are really excited to explore the other side of the city.
Thank you.
The heat is really getting to us.
It's really, really warm outside.
I think it probably like 30 degrees, probably more, but like in between there comes like this breeze, so it's quite like bearable.
Yeah, we can't complain.
We just went into like the most amazing like antique store that had so much like jewelry and cool like bracelets
and necklaces and oh, I really wanted the black beaded necklace that I tried on.
We didn't have cash on hand.
Yeah, we didn't end up buying them, but I think we're gonna regret it one day.
Yeah.
We are now walking over the Galata Bridge again, and we are now gonna take the ferry over to the Asian side, so we're just going
to a terminal, I guess.
We
have arrived in Asia!
Oh my god, I can't believe that this city is divided into two continents, and I didn't know that before coming here.
It definitely feels different here than the European side, and we're excited to see what's going on here.
We are kind of in desperate need of some hydration, and maybe something to eat.
We've been like walking, and it's very warm.
Yeah, but yeah, it's a bit more local here.
We feel like a bit more touristic on the other side, but yeah, we'll find out.
Oh,
that's a good cup of iced latte.
Very good.
So yummy.
Wow.
We did a bit of shopping.
I ended up buying the leather jacket that I tried on.
I was like in between because I own a Leather jacket, but this one was so different.
This one is a little bit more like a blazer and just like a little bit more fitted, and I really, really like wearing leather
jackets, so I know that I'm gonna be using this one a lot.
And my dad, I bought very cute.
They're really cute.
Yeah, summer, yeah.
And then the green dress.
Oh, she looked gorgeous in that dress.
She's actually gonna switch and wear it now.
Yeah.
Because we wanna take some nice pictures.
So yeah, she's gonna change, and we're gonna try and find a place to eat.
She's craving some durung.
We're gonna see if we can find a nice place to have dinner at.
I don't know if we're gonna do it here in the Asian side or if we will go back to Europe.
Yeah, we'll see.
We made it back to Karaköy.
And now we are searching for a fish wrap that we are kind of craving.
We wanted to try it
out.
We got our fish wraps, and now we are gonna taste them.
Okay.
The fish is very crunchy.
Oh my goodness.
So many flavours.
Yeah.
Wow, it's really good.
Also, the aftertaste is like more spicy.
Oh my goodness.
Okay, I'm impressed.
Yeah.
You need to check out this place if you are in Istanbul.
Oh my god, there's a cat here.
Hello.
That's something I love about Istanbul.
Because it's like filled with kitty cats.
Yeah.
Everywhere.
So cute.
And they feed them and give them water.
I think just the people living here, like Turkish people, like take really good care of the cats here.
So it's very beautiful.
Well guys, I really hope you guys enjoyed watching our Istanbul vlog, and remember to go and follow Mahda on Instagram and TikTok.
I will link it down below.
We really enjoyed our trip here in Istanbul.
Yeah, it's been so amazing.
It's so different from anything I've ever experienced.
Yeah, and this city is so beautiful, and I mean, we just had so much fun, and we ate so much good food.
It was a short trip, but I feel like we kind of got to experience it quite well.
Like, yeah, get a good idea of the city of India.
But maybe next time we will like stay for a bit longer if we want to, like, you know, be able to, because it's such a big city.
Yeah.
So yeah, thank you so much for watching, and I will see you next week.
You.